#### **Contact Info**



+1 617 752 1995



explosive0105@gmail.com



pedros930122



live:.cid.e67199ba9bde67a0

#### Certifications









## Skills

Typescript, React, Vue

Python, Django, FastAPI

Cosmos, Substrate, Smart Contract

# Pedro Salazar

# Senior Fullstack | Blockchain Core engineer

A key strength is the **continuous hunger** for innovative solutions and new technologies.

### INTRODUCTION

Proactive and creative software engineer with 8 years of experience in **web2** and **web3**. I like to learn new technology and develop quality products. Well-versed in creating scalable and optimized product. Personally like **React.js** and **Python**.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Senior Full Stack Engineer

DecorMatters | 2019 - 2022 | Remote

An software company in California

- Took part in the development of the web app development
- Responsible for providing the POC of the app workflow.
- Responsible for mentoring a junior and maintaining the architecture
- Responsible for code review.

#### **Web3 Engineer**

Enjin | 2018-2019 | Remote

A company building an ecosystem around gamers using blockchain technology

- Took part in game item marketplace development, azure hero badges and web wallet development project
- Improved the traffic of the existing project by 60%.
- · Responsible for smart contract auditing

#### **Full Stack Engineer**

X-Team | 2014-2018 | Remote

An innovative outsourcing company keep moving forward

- Launched 6+ websites in e-commerce, e-health, landing pages and production websites
- Mentored 4+ interns and junior developers to keep the quality of the product
- · Responsible for code review and test

### **EDUCATION**

2008 - 2012

University of California, Los Angeles

B.S.Computer Science

Studied about DIP and NLP